{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Greenhouse Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40349/":{"taskOID":40349,"originalTaskOID":40349,"setID":643,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4490,"questionDisplayText":"Style of Greenhouse","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What style greenhouse do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":827,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Arch","answerDisplayText":"Arch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4990,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Quonset","answerDisplayText":"Quonset","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2703,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gabled","answerDisplayText":"Gabled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":875,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Atrium","answerDisplayText":"Atrium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3520,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lean-to","answerDisplayText":"Lean-to","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4499,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Oval","answerDisplayText":"Oval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5436,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Round","answerDisplayText":"Round","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3279,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Installed against house","answerDisplayText":"Installed against house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2638,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Freestanding","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4809,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Portable","answerDisplayText":"Portable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4492,"questionDisplayText":"Additional Greenhouse Options","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What other features do you want in your greenhouse? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1021,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Benches","answerDisplayText":"Benches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5610,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Shade cloth","answerDisplayText":"Shade cloth","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Misting system","answerDisplayText":"Misting system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heating","answerDisplayText":"Heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6249,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Tables","answerDisplayText":"Tables","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":904,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Automatic window openers","answerDisplayText":"Automatic window openers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1289,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Ceiling Fan","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3616,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Line voltage thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Line voltage thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2999,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Hi-low recording thermometer","answerDisplayText":"Hi-low recording thermometer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2254,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Eshaust fan w/louvers","answerDisplayText":"Eshaust fan w/louvers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2817,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Glass storm door","answerDisplayText":"Glass storm door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4745,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Plumbing/water","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing/water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2892,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Gutters","answerDisplayText":"Gutters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4490,"questionDisplayText":"Style of Greenhouse","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What style greenhouse do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":827,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Arch","answerDisplayText":"Arch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4990,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Quonset","answerDisplayText":"Quonset","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2703,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gabled","answerDisplayText":"Gabled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":875,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Atrium","answerDisplayText":"Atrium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3520,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lean-to","answerDisplayText":"Lean-to","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4499,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Oval","answerDisplayText":"Oval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5436,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Round","answerDisplayText":"Round","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3279,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Installed against house","answerDisplayText":"Installed against house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2638,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Freestanding","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4809,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Portable","answerDisplayText":"Portable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":827,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Arch","answerDisplayText":"Arch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4990,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Quonset","answerDisplayText":"Quonset","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2703,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gabled","answerDisplayText":"Gabled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":875,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Atrium","answerDisplayText":"Atrium","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3520,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lean-to","answerDisplayText":"Lean-to","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4499,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Oval","answerDisplayText":"Oval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5436,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Round","answerDisplayText":"Round","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3279,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Installed against house","answerDisplayText":"Installed against house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2638,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Freestanding","answerDisplayText":"Freestanding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4809,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Portable","answerDisplayText":"Portable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4492,"questionDisplayText":"Additional Greenhouse Options","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What other features do you want in your greenhouse? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1021,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Benches","answerDisplayText":"Benches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5610,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Shade cloth","answerDisplayText":"Shade cloth","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Misting system","answerDisplayText":"Misting system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heating","answerDisplayText":"Heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6249,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Tables","answerDisplayText":"Tables","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":904,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Automatic window openers","answerDisplayText":"Automatic window openers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1289,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Ceiling Fan","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3616,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Line voltage thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Line voltage thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2999,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Hi-low recording thermometer","answerDisplayText":"Hi-low recording thermometer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2254,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Eshaust fan w/louvers","answerDisplayText":"Eshaust fan w/louvers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2817,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Glass storm door","answerDisplayText":"Glass storm door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4745,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Plumbing/water","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing/water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2892,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Gutters","answerDisplayText":"Gutters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1021,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Benches","answerDisplayText":"Benches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5610,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Shade cloth","answerDisplayText":"Shade cloth","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Misting system","answerDisplayText":"Misting system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Heating","answerDisplayText":"Heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6249,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Tables","answerDisplayText":"Tables","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":904,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Automatic window openers","answerDisplayText":"Automatic window openers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1289,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Ceiling Fan","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3616,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Line voltage thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Line voltage thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2999,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Hi-low recording thermometer","answerDisplayText":"Hi-low recording thermometer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2254,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Eshaust fan w/louvers","answerDisplayText":"Eshaust fan w/louvers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2817,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Glass storm door","answerDisplayText":"Glass storm door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4745,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Plumbing/water","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing/water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2892,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Gutters","answerDisplayText":"Gutters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/40349/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40349,"taskName":"Greenhouse or Conservatorium - Build","taskDescription":"Build a Greenhouse or Conservatorium","xmTaskDescriptor":"Greenhouse Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":108,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Conservatorium Build enclosure steel greenhouses","textMessagingName":"Build Greenhouse","rolloverLongDesc":"Either custom or kit built onsite of ready made units brought in by truck \u0026 installed onsite.","rolloverShortDesc":"For plants. Separate category for sunrooms.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a Greenhouse or Conservatorium.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Greenhouse Building \u0026 Construction \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Build a Greenhouse","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":37,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Greenhouse Build","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Greenhouse or Conservatorium - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Greenhouse Project","urlName":"Greenhouse-or-Conservatorium-Build","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Greenhouse Builders - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Reviews, Costs","searchKeywords":"Conservatorium,Build,enclosure,steel,greenhouses,construction,free,outbuilding,green,building,out,freestanding,Greenhouse,addition","emcCategoryOid":-12063,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":643,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}